While safety improvements might have been made to our streets in recent years, transport studies also show declines in pedestrian mobility, especially among young children.
虽然近年来我们的街道在安全方面可能有所改善，但交通研究也显示，行人的出行能力在下降，在年幼的孩子中尤为明显。
Many parents say there’s too much traffic on the roads for their children to walk safely to school, so they pack them into the car instead.
许多家长说，路上车太多，孩子没法安全地步行上学，所以他们改为把孩子塞进车里，开车送去上学。
Dutch authors Thalia Verkade and Marco te Brömmelstroet are bothered by facts like these.
荷兰作者塔利娅·费尔卡德和马尔科·特·布罗梅尔斯特鲁特对这样的事实感到困扰。
In their new book Movement: How to Take Back Our Streets and Transform Our Lives, they call for a rethink of our streets and the role they play in our lives.
在他们的新书《出行：如何夺回我们的街道，改变我们的生活》中，他们呼吁重新思考我们的街道，以及街道在我们生活中所扮演的角色。
Life on city streets started to change decades ago.
城市街道上的生活早在几十年前就开始改变了。
Whole neighbourhoods were destroyed to make way for new road networks and kids had to play elsewhere.
整片整片的街区被拆毁，为新的道路网络让路，孩子们只好到别处去玩。
Some communities fought back.
一些社区奋起反抗。
Most famously, a Canadian journalist who lived in Manhattan in the 1950s led a campaign to stop the destruction of her local park.
最有名的是，一位20世纪50年代住在曼哈顿的加拿大记者领导了一场运动，阻止当地公园被毁。
Describing her alarm at its proposed replacement with an expressway, Jane Jacobs called on her mayor to champion “New York as a decent place to live, and not just rush through.”
简·雅各布斯表达了她对有人提议用高速公路取代这座公园的担忧，呼吁市长捍卫“纽约作为一个宜居之地，而不只是一个匆匆路过的地方”。
Similar campaigns occurred in Australia in the late 1960s and 1970s as well.
20世纪60年代末和70年代，澳大利亚也发生过类似的运动。
Although these campaigns were widespread, the reality is that the majority of western cities were completely redesigned around the needs of the motor car.
尽管这些运动很普遍，但现实是，大多数西方城市都完全围绕汽车的需要重新设计了。
The number of cars on roads has been increasing rapidly.
路上的汽车数量一直在迅速增加。
In Australia we now have over twenty million cars for just over twenty-six million people, among the highest rates of car ownership in the world.
在澳大利亚，如今我们2600万出头的人口拥有2000多万辆汽车，汽车拥有率位居世界前列。
We invest a lot in roads that help us rush through, but we fail to account for the true costs.
我们在能让我们匆匆通过的道路上投入很多，却没有把真正的代价考虑在内。
Do we really recognise what it costs us as a society when children can’t move safely around our communities?
当孩子们无法在社区里安全走动时，我们真的意识到这让整个社会付出了什么代价吗？
The authors of Movement have it right: it’s time to think differently about that street outside your front door.
《出行》的作者说得对：是时候换个角度看待你家门外的那条街了。